http://www.stationeryxpress.com/privacy-policy

Oversized Stationery
Long Flat Cards - 4.5” x 8.5”
Oversized Flat Cards - 4.8" x 7"
Your Logo Printed
Your Logo Printed Flat Cards (Min. qty 200 Cards)
Your Logo Printed Fold Notes (Min. qty 200 Notes)
Lower Quantities (50-150 Cards/Notes)
Champagne Flute Glasses
Wine Glasses (with and without stems)
Stationery
20% OFF Monogrammed Sale!!
Envelopes Only
View All Stationery...
Corporate & Logo
Your Logo Embossed
Flat Cards (Min. Qty 200)
Fold Notes (Min. Qty 200)
Your Logo Printed
Flat Cards (Min Qty 200)
Fold Notes (Min Qty 200)
Lower Quantities (50-150)
Affordable Gifts
20% OFF Sale!
Contact Us
Blog
Stationery
20% OFF Monogrammed Sale!!
Envelopes Only
View All Stationery...
Corporate & Logo
Your Logo Embossed
Flat Cards (Min. Qty 200)
Fold Notes (Min. Qty 200)
Your Logo Printed
Flat Cards (Min Qty 200)
Fold Notes (Min Qty 200)
Lower Quantities (50-150)
Affordable Gifts
20% OFF Sale!
Contact Us
Blog
Home
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for StationeryXpress.com.
This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing StationeryXpress does not engage in selling any form of customer data, customer profile or any other customer information to outside marketing firms or other third parties. Ever. Period. We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will never sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
We may use or add pictures of your completed order/items to various product pages for example purposes only. If you do not wish to have a photo of your completed item/order on our website, please contact us and we will remove it immediately.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time and for any reason. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email, phone, text message, live chat message or the Contact Us page on our website. You have the following rights below by using this website, StationeryXpress.com:
• The right to know. See what personal information or data we have about you, if any, and how it is used and shared.
• The right to change. You may change/correct/update any data or information we have about you.
• The right to delete. Have us delete any data or personal information collected that we have about you.
• The right to express any concern you have about our use of your data.
• The right to opt-out of any future contacts from us.
• The right to non-discrimination for exercising your CCPA rights.
Security We take credit card data security very seriously. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. All transactions take place on our secure and encrypted 256-bit encryption SSL server using Braintree (A PayPal Service) transaction processing security. Braintree is a Validated Level 1 PCI DSS Compliant Service Provider.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom/top of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment and are password protected.
Registration In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration or guest check-out form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services or your order on our site in which you have expressed interest.
Orders We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is only used for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
Cookies We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access and experience on our website and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site nor is any information shared/rented/sold to any third-party.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy or you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-800-506-3884 or via email at orders@stationeryxpress.com.
×
© 1993-2020 StationeryXpress
